Hello hello viewers welcome back to trading
state if you are active in the market and
invest in Frida then we have to know the
name of our company whose name is Chanel friends
this company is this company
it is in discussion from few days because of its two
20% packets as you
can see its chart on the screen
so the Khana survey hit an upper circuit of 20%
closing 170 and
next it opens it is Aravan
then around 194 and this one which is 190 comes
and the process happens at 205 rupees
with cent off what happened
set such a big increase in the share of this government company
so friends if you go to Google and
search about General Insurance
then you can see here that a
news came in the market that the company
named General Insurance which is a dormant company is going to be
privatized it will do this
in the comment spam it will do
20 minutes
so friends due to this news so much circuit was hit in this company
it maintained two circuits in half an hour
before that if you will see its movement this  If you
look at the trend of the topic, you will see a normal sluggish
fall.
You will not see anything special in Delhi time. It has
not yet done its P at the vote level.
Now you can see that this car
toys 272 is running in the range of 10 till now.
Hello friends, what happened because of one news
that it got upset, so behind this,
dirty friends, let's talk about its share
holding pattern, which you can see
that I have 10 President of India, that is, pass.
If we talk about it, it has been confirmed, which is
11.75 and
12 class number of last year, no doubt, there
is public public in it, friends, see, as
you can see, only 2.2 Shyam is available, that is,
this company has very less
or very less number of seats available in the market, so if
anything goes in it, it can die immediately,
so friends, you can
settle well in it. If you get to see more, then
this company is doing 18 on the entire industry.
Friends, please subscribe,
if you want to
hear the news, please subscribe.  Do not get pregnant on the best stock, after all
friends, whether to invest in it or not,
this is the addition, this video has been
made only for the question professor, if
you like this video then
like the video, subscribe to the channel, so
I will meet you in the next video
with someone's staff